# TAYLOR RADTKE

www.taylorradtke.com

### **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.

# **SUMMARY**

Taylor Radtke is a creative mind who specializes in minimal design that displays a bold message. After three plus years of marketing in the service industry, Taylor takes his social skills mastered from constructing cocktails through college to creating a finished project that his client truly loves. A mastermind at social media marketing, with a concentration on an age demographic of 18-35. Taylor has a great latitude of culture due to his upbringing in Southern California then transitioning to the mid-Atlantic region to further his career and education. Recently Taylor has devoted his time to mastering the world of front-end web development and design. His passion for web design comes from viewing it as a functional piece of art, and striving to let his mind continue to share the beauty of digital

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Web Developer/Designer, The Creative Group

Washington, DC — September 2015 - Present

- Used creative ability to transform a word document's content into well-structured landing pages
- Attention to detail in the development process
- Designing/Developing social media elements for multiple outlets
- Excelling in time management to productivity ratio
- Generating organic traffic from user friendly design

# Marketing, Promotions Manager, Sam Miller's Oyster Bar

Richmond, VA — 2012 - 2015

- Booked entertainment for weekly events
- Designing and maintaining website
- Designing menus and promotional flyers
- Meeting with liquor representatives to coordinate events

### **EDUCATION**

# **General Assembly DC**

Front-End Web Development — 2015-Pres

### **Virginia Commonwealth University**

Information Systems (B.A) — 2011-2014

# J. Sargeant Reynolds

Business (A.A.S) — 2009-2011

### **SKILLS**

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3 JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, AngularJS Node.js, PHP, Python, Django
- Operating System: Windows, Apple iOS, Linux
- Software: Adobe (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Edge Animate, Dreamweaver, Lightroom, Flash, Fireworks, After Effects), Microsoft (Office, Excel, SharePoint, Publisher, Access, Word, PowerPoint, Visio), Corel (Draw, Paint), iMovie, Windows Movie Maker
- Website CMS Tools: Wordpress, Twitter Bootstrap, Foundation, Git, Github, Bower, Drupal, Grunt, Gulp, Jekyll, MailChimp API

# **Awards**

• Paul Harris Fellow, Rotary International